[Music]
hey what's up it's Oliver your fwp of
FWD so for today's
video number one 100%
refund
[Music]
number two you can claim up to three
times for example
milance in the
fure up
to number three 20% claim for minor
critical
ill number four life insurance in the
event of you passed away
benefits number five flexible payment
terms it is not a lifetime payment
fible 10 20 years of payment per covered
up to 75 years old lastly number six is
waiver of premium if ever diagnostical
illness and you don't need to pay the
remaining years the insurance
compan for example 20
years and in the first year diag
critical illness the rest 19 years
[Music]
is this health insurance called set for
health critical illness insurance and
all of that benefits I FD your happiness
is a reflection of your health once
again this is Oliver your fwp of FWD
thank you guys for watching
bye-bye